See you, Origami!
Okay, later!
Dad? Mom?
Dad?
Mom?
It was... you!
I'll never forgive you!
I'll kill you... I swear, I'll kill you!
Someday, I will!
Good morning, Shido.
Sleeping together... It's a dream.
Sleeping together... It's romance.
If only that slumber lasted forever,
it would be paradise.
What the hell are you two doing
so early in the morning?!
"Episode Six:
'Crossroads'"
Are you seriously engaging
in lewd acts like this
under the same roof as your little sister?
I-It's a misunderstanding! Right, Natsumi?
Shido's such a perv.
Hey, how did you transform
to your adult form?!
Speaking of which, I never told you.
About Natsumi, that is.
Was the seal incomplete or something?
No, the seal itself was a success.
Then, is something impacting
her mental state?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
You know, Natsumi's kinda mentally weak.
--Oh...
--Hey, now.
What are you two whispering about?
Don't leave this poor girl out of the loop!
Listen here. Do something about
transforming over every little thing!
Don't be so jealous that Shido fell for me.
It's not my fault that your body
is inferior to mine.
Wh--?! Who you calling a munchkin?!
I'll have you know I'm in a growth spurt!
Munchkin, huh?
Don't you dare laugh!
I didn't even call you that!
You piss me off!
Origami still hasn't come?
That... was one of DEM's CR-units...
What does this mean?
Why did she...?
Stand!
Bow!
Sit!
Um, before attendance, I have
some sad news to announce.
Eh, what's wrong, Tammie?
Did matchmaking not work out?
Were you catfished?!
That's so lame!
Ahem! Well, actually...
Origami Tobiichi will be transferring
due to unexpected circumstances.
Transferring?!
Trans... fer?
Hold on a second! Origami?!
What do you mean?!
I don't know all the details myself.
I got a call from her out of nowhere saying,
"I'm transferring. I'll send
you the forms later."
No... What school is she going to?!
Uh! Well, about that...
She said some school in England...
England? Don't tell me...
Itsuka?
U-Um... My stomach!
My stomach hurts, so...!
--Shi--
--You don't have to come, I'll be fine!
Ow, ow, ow...
Argh! Why do I have to be like this?!
And here I finally woke up early enough!
I never meant to wake him up like that...
Thanks for the tea, Natsumi!
U-Um, do you need something from me?
Um, well...
Why did she even come to my room?
What could it be?
D-Don't tell me she bears a grudge
and came to get revenge!
Uh, N-Natsumi...
Since you just moved in, you probably
don't know the city that well...
That's right! I was fooling Shido by
impersonating her precious friend!
B-But, it's not like I know
all there is to know...
...so I might not be all too helpful...
She waited until the others
were gone to get revenge!
But if you're fine with it, do you want
me to show you around the city?
Huh?!
I've always spent this
time of day all by myself...
And since you're here now,
I was hoping we could talk a lot...
Plus...
W-We're friends, after all!
Whoa! I've gotta marry this girl!
Y-You'll show me around the city?
Let's go! Hurry, let's
go! Let's go right now!
The number you have dialed is out
of the service area, not powered--
Why won't she pick up?!
Please be here, Origami...
Good thing I made it inside...
"Tobiichi"
Origami, it's me!
Answer if you're there!
It's open!
Origami!
Where in the world did
you run off to, Origami?
--Ooh!
--Your lunch looks yummy, Kotori!
My brother made it for me!
Let's eat!
You can't contact Shido?
He's in school, right?
It seems he left early after
hearing Origami transferred.
What was that?
Gone missing with timing
like that? Very suspicious...
And the others?
Tohka, the Yamai Sisters, and Miku
are having lunch at their schools.
Natsumi and Yoshino
went out to play in the city.
I see... I hate to make them worry,
but we can't fool them forever.
Find Shido before Tohka
and the others get home.
This is...
I went to Origami's and...
Origami?!
Hey, Origami! What are you...?
Water. Aren't you thirsty?
Eh?
Um...
Stop! All right!
I'll have some, so let
me drink it like normal!
Nice and slow...
F-For the time being,
could you get me out of this?
That I can't do.
You... joined DEM?
Yes.
And abducting me?
Was that by Westcott's orders?
I brought you here of my own volition.
DEM is not aware of these actions of mine.
It had to be done.
In order to keep you out of it,
this was the surest method to take.
Hold on a minute. Keep me out?
Out of what?!
My fight with the Spirits.
By Spirits, you mean...?
Of course. Tohka and the others
are no exception.
I thought you were after the Spirit
who killed your parents!
They have nothing to do with it!
They're Spirits all the same.
If we're to stop more humans
like me from being created,
we cannot allow them to continue existing.
Tohka and them aren't
even detected as Spirits!
You said you didn't have
to go after them anymore!
That was a Self-Defense Force decision.
It has nothing to do with me now.
Hey, Origami.
It's been over half a year since
Tohka transferred to our school.
How time flies.
Those Spirits you guys used
to fight are part of society now.
They're all living like humans now.
And you... After seeing them all this time?
You saying they're not changed?
That once a Spirit, always a Spirit?!
That they're so dangerous,
they have to be killed?!
You don't think I get it?!
Tohka Yatogami and the other Spirits...
They're Spirits all the same.
They should feed my revenge, and yet...
I couldn't forgive myself for
slowly losing sight of that.
Five years ago, I swore to get
revenge on the Spirits, and yet...
I got so used to how things
are now... and that scares me.
The reason I joined DEM was
because I finally realized it.
That a life with Tohka Yatogami...
was one I came to accept.
And what's so wrong with that?!
You know as well as I do!
All they want is to live normal lives!
No... I can't allow that.
Not as long as they're Spirits.
I have to kill more than just Spirits.
I have to kill the one swayed
by emotions... myself.
By taking the life of Tohka Yatogami,
I will regain who I was.
Wait, Origami!
Please, wait!
And you're fine with this, Ike?
Allowing her to act on her own?
Doesn't matter to me.
She's finally showing some spunk.
No need to hinder the enthusiasm
of a young Wizard.
Spirits are what we're after in the end.
Only by letting a falling bomb drop
can one truly measure its power.
Aren't you curious to know how far she'll go?
Very well. I'll work behind the scenes.
You're displeased.
I can tell because your brows
wrinkle when you lie.
Eh?
Just kidding.
Don't be mad with me.
This time, I have another
target in mind for you.
Another target?
Yeah... Ratatoskr.
There's a certain ship that
will get in Origami's way...
...and I want you to stop it.
With Goetia, that is.
Shido leaving early means he's too weak.
We have to train him back into shape.
Agreement. He's a wimpy wimp.
Starting tomorrow, we'll
make him run all around.
I'm sure Shido had a reason for it.
Question. I heard that Master Origami
has transferred schools.
Could Shido leaving be related to that?
Yeah...
In fact, as soon as he heard
about it, Shido left at once.
I knew it! That smells fishy to me!
Smells fishy? I can't smell any fish!
No, that's not what I mean...
Hmm?
Tohka!
Kaguya!
Yuzuru!
It's an expression of love! Why run away?!
I-Is it?
That's right! Everyone's doing it these days!
Come on, you too!
Don't be fooled, my kinswoman!
Warning. I smell a liar.
I knew it! For starters, what are
you doing here anyways?
Oh, yes! I came to visit Darling,
but no one was there and it was boring!
And the house next door was empty, too!
Shido hasn't come home yet?
That whole Origami thing might
have something to do with this.
Agreement. I think we're on to something.
Sheesh! Tell me what's going on!
Did something happen to Darling?
Well, you see...
This is...
The spatial quake alarm, right?
Another Spirit has showed up then?
Curious. Shall we see who this Spirit is?
You can't do that! If the alarm
is sounding, we have to evacuate!
But Shido is--
No need for that.
Origami Tobiichi! What are you doing here?!
There is no spatial quake.
What do you mean? They're evacuating!
The alarm is sounding
because I requested it to.
Neither a Spirit nor the AST will show up.
What?! Why would you do something like that?!
"Comparison Complete"
"Origami Tobiichi"
In order to kill you all here.
What was that for?!
I said already. To kill you.
To kill all Spirits!
Those eyes... Why?
Why have you gone back to
before, Origami Tobiichi?!
Good on you to notice!
Admiration. That's our Master Origami.
Now then. How about explaining
what this is about?
Inquiry. Please answer us, Master Origami.
We don't want to fight you.
I don't have to answer anything!
Sandalphon!
Gabriel, Rondo!
You guys! Are you okay?!
Origami Tobiichi is serious.
If we don't kill her, we'll be killed.
--But...
--What are you doing, Tohka?!
Origami Tobiichi?! What's she doing there?!
It's incredible magic power!
She's on a whole new level than before!
Without their full Spirit armor,
Tohka and the others...
Fraxinus. Full power ahead.
We'll recover Tohka and them.
If it gets ugly, deploy the Yggdrafolium.
Back them up!
Roger!
What was that?!
We've been attacked!
Territory reduced 30 percent!
Enemy sighted at 3 o'clock!
It's an airship!
Are you serious?!
This is... DEM's...
At a time like this!
A transmission.
Transmission?
Said ship is trying to reach
Fraxinus through a transmission!
Connect us!
Roger!
Nice to meet you, I suppose.
Thank you for receiving me.
Ellen Mathers...
So you've heard of me then?
I'm honored, Kotori Itsuka.
What business does the world's
strongest Wizard have with us today?
If you want to drink tea, let's do
it later. I'm busy right now.
A vile organization's troublesome pawn
is picking a fight with our girls.
I've two things to say.
One. I'll give you up to three minutes.
Anyone who wants to live
should leave the ship at once.
You honestly believe you
can take down Fraxinus?
I'm saying I can't deny the
possibility it might happen.
Still, "Fraxinus"? The World Tree?
Elliot must have chosen the name?
Aren't you underestimating
Fraxinus a little bit?
With all due respect, perhaps you're
the one underestimating things.
Both Goetia's abilities... and my power.
So? You have more to say?
Yes, to the one who fled this conflict...
I have a message for Elliot.
A message?
Yes.
Elliot... Elliot! You damn traitor!
You turned your back on us and
our promise! Prepare yourself!
No matter where you hide, I will
find you! I will have your head!
That's all. Starting now,
I'll give you three minutes.
Please hurry and escape.
So she says.
We're up against humanity's best.
If you want to flee, that's fine by me.
Oh, please...
If I wanted to flee now, I would never
have followed you from the start.
Yes. Leaving you behind and running?
How is that any different than death?
Agreed! Humanity's greatest or not,
let's show her what we've got!
Your orders, Commander?
My will is written and good to go.
And the hard drive in my computer back
home is set to erase if I happen to die!
Of course, it's hard to pass up getting
punished by you for running--
There you have it.
Is that so? What a shame.
AR-008! Give three to six
parallel driving force!
Replenish magic power! Ready Mistilteinn!
Target: DEM airship Goetia!
Roger!
Kotori Itsuka... I thought you were
capable of rational thought, but...
Though you two don't share any blood,
you truly are Shido's little sister.
Best compliment ever.
Kannazuki! Deploy Yggdrafolium
one through twelve!
It's the world's strongest Wizard.
Be prepared, just in case!
I knew you would say that!
Let's clean up quickly here
and get to Tohka at once!
Replenishment complete!
Mistilteinn, ready to fire!
Enemy ship Goetia hasn't moved.
Sitting pretty for three minutes?
She's taking us lightly.
Mistilteinn, fire!
You're kidding! What was that speed?
They must have thinned out the
Territory surrounding the ship
to maximize their mobility.
And that driving force... They probably
used Territory to flick the ship aside.
You're saying that's possible?!
Theoretically, it could be done.
As expected of the immortal Mathers.
This is no time to be
impressed! She's coming!
Protect Territory! Brace for impact!
You've done it now! Prepare counterattack!
Yggdrafolium to mine mode!
Get them behind her!
Roger!
What now?!
It's... another bombardment!
Shit! Anyone?! Is anyone there?!
Anyone!
"Episode Seven:
'The Power Given'"